好的，以下就是方案。开始之前，让我们
All right. And here's the solution. To start off, let's
看看我们的forecast fragment查询。由于是两张表的join，
look at our forecast fragment query. Since it's a join
添加额外参数到我们的查询中
between two tables, it's really easy for us to add
是非常简单的。现在我们确保我们保持
additional parameters to our query. Now we make sure we keep
列标一致。现在我们在抓去天气条目时，同时
the column indices consistent. Now we've grabbed the latitude and
抓取经纬度。
longitude at the same time we're grabbing our weather entries.
下一步要做的是把
The next thing to do is to move the function
在地图中打开偏好地址的方法移到ForecastFragmen里去。
open preferred location in map over to forecast fragment. Instead of
我们不使用shared preference来获取这额值，而是
using shared preferences to get these values, we can actually
从ForecastAdapter获取指针。我们
get the cursor from the forecast adapter. We can get
可以让我们的指针移到一个合理的位置，
our cursor moved to a reasonable position, and then build
然后创建经纬度冒号连接的字符串。
our new string which is just latitude colon longitude. We'll
我们会在这里注释这是啥。最后，我们
leave our comment where it was. Finally, we just have
只要修好代码里一些小地方
to fix up a few things in the code and
就好了。好的，至少对于代码来讲，我们依然需要
that's it. Well, at least for the code. We still
在XML里做一些事儿。让我们在选项被选中时候把R.ID.action映射
need to do some work in XML. Let's move this R.ID.action
移动到ForecastFragment里。
map now over to forecast fragment inside of it on
现在我们要做一些XML的事儿。
options item selected. And now we've got to do some
让我们看看我们的主菜单。我们只要
XML work. Let's look at our main menu. We'll just
把这个动作映射项拉过来，然后把他
pull this action map item out, and we'll place it right
放入ForecastFragment里。好的。在此还有最后一步要做的。
into forecast fragment. All right. One more thing to do
Raito提到的事情之一是希望
while we're here. One of the things Raito talked about was
去除刷新菜单项。所以
wanting to get rid of the refresh menu item. So,
让我们直接注释掉他。当我们移除刷新项时，
let's just comment it out. When we remove that action refresh
我们或许也应当从我们的源码中注释掉他。
item, we should probably comment it out from our source
最后，毕竟，你不会知道什么时候还会用到他来
code too. After all, you never know when you'll want to
debug。所以，我们完成了。我们最终的app。
use that for debugging. So, there we have it. Our
再也没有刷新按钮。
final app. No longer having a refresh button. With a
而是带着一个新的令人兴奋的可以关闭天气提醒的设置。
new exciting setting to turn off and on weather notifications.
细节被好好照顾到。我希望你们享受构建Sunshine。
Details are taken care of. I hope you've enjoyed building
还剩很多事情可以在Sunshine里做。
Sunshine. There's still lots of things left to do in
比如，我们也应当在我们的界面中加入许多聪明
Sunshine. For example, we could also add a lot more intelligent
的东西。当然还有，我们可以
things to its user interface. And of course, we
让他在同步数据上变得更加智能。
could make it a lot smarter about synching data.
我也希望你们从构建Sunshine的练习中所学到的
And I hope the practices you've learned building Sunshine
会对你们将来的所有app有所帮助
will help you in all of your future applications